<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8000000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8000000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Antiquity Fair]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8000000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[The Antiquity Fair has rolled into town! Prepare yourself for fun and herculean prizes!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8000000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Haltet ein, oh weiser Stadthalter {PLAYERNAME}, wir beabsichtigen die schöne Helena aus den Klauen der Trojaner zu befreien! Solltet Ihr uns unterstützen, ist Euch unser ewiger Dank gewiss!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8000000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Als Nyx uns in der vergangenen Dämmerstunde heimsuchte, eröffnete sich mir ein fantastischer Plan: Im Bauche eines hölzernen Pferdes passieren wir versteckt die Tore von Troja! Könnt Ihr uns mit Holz versorgen?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8000000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Was für ein stattliches Ross. Sobald Troja erstürmt ist, dürft Ihr Eure Stadt damit schmücken!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8001000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8001000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Blockhütten-Expo]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8001000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Saul Bunyan's in town with the Log Cabin Expo! Swing your axe and join the fun!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8001000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Endlich ist es soweit, die weltberühmte Blockhütten-Expo kommt in Deine Stadt! Ich bin Jack Lumber, amtierender Holzhack-Weltmeister und Organisator der Expo.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8001000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Ich würde ja liebend gerne selbst Hand an die Axt legen, aber aus Zeitgründen würde ich Arbeitsteilung vorschlagen! Du besorgst Holz in rauen Mengen und ich schustere die Blockhütten zusammen!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8001000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Herrlich, fast wie im fernen Kanada, meiner trauten Heimat!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8002000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8002000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Weekly Market]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8002000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Your residents sure love fresh veggies. They're sure to give you goodies in return!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8002000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Local, freshly-grown fruit and vegetables are chock full of nutrients! Every delivery comes with a little side of gossip, too! I'll organize a weekly market so that everyone can enjoy fresh produce. What do think?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8002000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[First, we have to expand the Event Plaza. We need a solid foundation for the market stands. Can you help us? Great, I'll be watching for your delivery.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8002000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Great job! The Event Plaza looks perfect. A masterpiece, if I do say so myself.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8002000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Everything's ready - the only thing left to do is fill the market stands with local delicacies. I'll bring the goods to the man and I'll be watching for your delivery.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8002000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[The stands are totally empty! Now your residents are healthy and happy.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8003000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8003000.layer.name"><![CDATA[La Tomatina]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8003000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[The Tomatina Fest is back, along with the infamous tomato fight. Look out for great prizes!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8003000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Kennst Du das spanische "Tomatina-Fest“? Eine riesige Tomatenschlacht in unserer Stadt! Das wird ein Spaß!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8003000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Bevor das "Tomatina-Fest" beginnen kann, solltest Du den Festplatz vorbereiten! Ein paar Tribünen und Zäune aus Holz sollten reichen.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8003000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Das sieht doch super aus! Der Festplatz ist hergerichtet und schon kann es losgehen!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8003000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Klasse! "La Tomatina" kann steigen! Alles was jetzt noch fehlt sind die Tomaten!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8003000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Das war ein Spaß! Danke, dass Du uns geholfen hast, das "Tomatina-Fest" zu organisieren! Als Dank haben die Teilnehmer eine kleine Überraschung für Dich!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Circus Fettuccine]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[The circus is in town! Help the Fettuccine Brothers put on a great show and some great prizes could be yours.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[The famous Fettuccine Brothers have rolled into the city with their circus! Maybe we can help them out. Come on, let's go take a look.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[We need to polish up this circus wagon! To do this, start making lumber and wood shavings in your lumber mill.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[That looks a lot better.  The Fettuccine Brothers have a reward for you!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Let's feed the animals a hearty meal, so they'll perform even better! On the farm, we can grow hay for the horses and crops for the monkeys!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[The animals are stuffed! The Fettuccine Brothers have a reward for you!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Hay]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[HAY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[Circus horses love fresh hay!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.goods.goodname.61002"><![CDATA[Wood chips]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.goods.goodname.61002.capital"><![CDATA[WOOD CHIPS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8004000.goods.tooltip.61002"><![CDATA[Perfect for tired circus animals that want to curl up and nap!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Farmer's Market]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Your residents sure love fresh veggies. They're sure to give you goodies in return!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[The residents of your city have requested a farmer's market. Let's put one together!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[First, we have to get the market ready. Can you go gather the materials needed?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[The first step is done. Looks great!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Just a few improvements here and there are needed. Can you go get some more building materials?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Awesome! The stands are done! The market can open!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Plant some delicious, healthy vegetables to sell at the farmer's market. How does this sound? You deliver the vegetables and I'll sell them!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[The residents love the farmer's market! Great!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Your residents are buying left and right! We're gonna need more! Let's get the stands full!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Selling high-quality wares to happy customers out in the fresh air - can't ask for anything better!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Your residents still don't have enough! Do you think you can deliver more products?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Well done! We've sold everything. The people are happy! We should do this again soon!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Corn]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[CORN]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[Fresh corn, delicious and organic!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Carrots]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[CARROTS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8005000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Crunchy root vegetables are great for soups or a healthy snack!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Lumberjack Finals]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Do you have what it takes for the Lumberjack Finals? Prove it and reap the sweet rewards!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Great news! The Lumberjack Finals are coming to your city! Help us get ready - it's gonna be so much fun!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Let's get to work; there's so much to do! First we have to get the event plaza ready: You get started on the materials and I'll organize the rest!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Nice job! The plaza looks great! Let's keep going!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[We're still missing wood for the sawhorses. Don't forget, we'll also need logs for the contest in your lumber yard!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Perfect! Everything is ready, the Lumberjack Finals can begin!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Amazing! Look at those athletes, they're chopping wood at lightning speed! Quick, we'll need more logs and materials!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[The first few contests are done and the tournament is a complete success. Way to go!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Oh no! The axes needed for the contest are late! Maybe we can borrow some from your residents? Please ask them when you go to collect their rent.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Whew, just in time! Thanks to you and your residents, the tournament can continue!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[We'll need more axes for the finale of the axe throwing contest. The athletes look tired already. Send them some power bars from your bakery!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Isn't this great?! The Lumberjack Finals were a total success! You've certainly earned this reward! See you next time!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.goodname.61002"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.goodname.61002.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.tooltip.61002"><![CDATA[The ideal material for the Lumberjack Finals.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Axe]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[AXE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Sharp blades, nonslip handle: A true championship axe!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.goodname.61005"><![CDATA[Power bar]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.goodname.61005.capital"><![CDATA[POWER BAR]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8006000.goods.tooltip.61005"><![CDATA[An energy boost for tired lumberjacks baked from the finest grains!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Halloween]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Don't be a scaredy-cat!  If all goes well, you'll get more treats than tricks this Halloween.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Take a look at your calendar. Halloween is just around the corner! Help us prepare a Halloween festival that's sure to give you goosebumps!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[The Event Plaza needs to be reinforced for Halloween, since there will be so many kids present. Bring us some stable logs and roof beams!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Excellent! The Event Plaza is strong enough to hold a herd of elephants!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[The forecast says that Halloween is going to be a dry night. But let's not take any chances - gather more roof beams and logs to build a canopy!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Fantastic! The Even Plaza is ready. We can let in the kids!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[What's a Halloween without pumpkin carving? And tomatoes to give the Event Plaza a gruesome, bloody look.  Give us a hand with that!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Ew, gross! The tomato blood looks just like the real thing!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Halloween is a huge hit with the kids! Look at them lining up. We need more pumpkins and tomatoes as soon as possible!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Great! The kids are having a spooktacular time. What a party!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[The kids want to dress up! Your citizens will surely donate old fabric the next time that they pay rent.  You can produce wood for broomsticks in your lumber mill. ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[You did it!! The kids are ready for some trick-or-treat fun!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Last, but not least, we need candy for the perfect Halloween! The kids stream from house to house gathering goodies.  Help them out!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Yum, so many treats! The kids are going to be so happy. ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[Oh no! What's wrong? À hole has opened up in the middle of the Event Plaza - something is trying to climb out! Quick, grab some logs and roof beams! We've got to close it up!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[Phew! That was a close call! But I think we've still got a ghost on our hands now!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[Boo, you wannabe mayors make me so mad! This piece of land belongs to me, Ebenezer Moneybags! Hm, but for a wooden chest full of gold I'd sell it to you in a flash! Build me one!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[What a lovely chest. But it's empty! Is this some kind of trick?!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[Now listen up, wannabe mayor! There are gold nuggets lying around all over your city.  Get enough to fill the chest and I'll be satisfied! You've got my word!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[Wooo! Beautiful gold! The land is yours. You can take these old building permits, I won't be needing them anymore!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Halloween Pumpkin]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[HALLOWEEN PUMPKIN]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[This special type of pumpkin is perfectly suited for carving!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61002"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61002.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.tooltip.61002"><![CDATA[Strengthen your Event Plaza for Halloween with these stable logs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Candy]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[CANDY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Yum! Gumdrops, lollipops, and chocolate! What would Halloween be without candy?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61006"><![CDATA[Fabric]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61006.capital"><![CDATA[FABRIC]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.tooltip.61006"><![CDATA[You can make all sorts of scary costumes from old fabric!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Gold nuggets]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[GOLD NUGGETS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[Sparkling golden nuggets! Too bad the ghost wants them!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Glowing Gaps]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8007000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Close the glowing gaps in the streets to collect gold nuggets!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Circus Fettuccine]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[The circus is in town! Help the Fettuccine Brothers put on a great show and some great prizes could be yours.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[The famous Fettuccine Brothers have arrived in the city with their circus! Maybe we can help them out. Let's go take a look!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[The animal enclosures and wagons need to be cleaned and repaired. You'll need to produce sawdust and beams in your lumber mill!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Wow, that looks great! It takes happy animals to put on a great show in the ring.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Speaking of the circus rings... The sawdust and support beams look a little worn out. Let's switch them out! Can you get me some new beams and more sawdust from your lumber mill?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Superb! The circus rings are ready! Onwards!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[The circus ponies look hungry! You'll never believe how much these little guys can eat! Get them some carrots and hay from your farm!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Fantastic! The ponies are happy and full. It's almost time for the show!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[You won't believe it! The camels have eaten the clown band's costumes! Let's go collect fabric in town, so that we can make some new costumes. Hurry up! The show must go on!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[What colorful costumes! Those will be perfect! Great job!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Uh oh! The circus billboards are missing! The delivery service says that the must have fallen off of the truck. You need to look for them on the streets! You can't expect an audience, if no one knows about the show!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Awesome! You saved the show! It was a complete success! The circus is sure to be back in town soon!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Hay]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[HAY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[Healthy and nutritious food for all the circus animals!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61002"><![CDATA[Sawdust]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61002.capital"><![CDATA[SAWDUST]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.tooltip.61002"><![CDATA[Perfect bedding for tired circus animals!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Carrots]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[CARROTS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Circus ponies love crunchy carrots!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61006"><![CDATA[Fabric]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61006.capital"><![CDATA[FABRIC]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.tooltip.61006"><![CDATA[Use this fabric to make new clown costumes!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Circus billboards]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[CIRCUS BILLBOARDS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[No billboards, no visitors! The circus needs advertising!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[CIRCUS BILLBOARDS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8008000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[No billboards, no visitors! The circus needs advertising!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Antiquity Fair]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Make way for the Antiquity Fair! Enjoy a taste of the ancient times and win great prizes. Onward!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Greetings, Mayor {PLAYERNAME}! Our Antiquity Fair was so successful the last time that we decided to come around again. Can you help us with the preparations?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[We'll need to build the stage in the authentic ancient style. We'll need lots of wood to do that!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Wonderful! The stage is done!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Time to build up a theater around the stage. Looks like we'll need more wood.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Wow! The ancient-style open-air theater looks great.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[The players are already practicing in the background. A few cheesy breakfast biscuits should give them the energy they need to make it through the day!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Full bellies and smiles all around, excellent work!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[The warriors are still hungry. A hearty stew should help boost their energy. We'll need carrots and potatoes.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Everything tasted so delicious and everyone now has a belly full of warm food.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Thanks a million, Mayor! If we could just get a little more gold, then we might be able to make a replica of the Trojan Horse. That would be a big hit at the festival!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Fantastic! The festival was a complete success. The audience was completely enthralled; we filled every seat in the house.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Carrots]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[CARROTS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[Every stew needs plenty of carrots!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61002"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61002.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.tooltip.61002"><![CDATA[Giant logs are used to stabilize the festival grounds.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61008"><![CDATA[Cheese slices]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61008.capital"><![CDATA[CHEESE SLICES]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.tooltip.61008"><![CDATA[Real Workers can have a real big appetite! You've probably got some leftover cheese, right?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61009"><![CDATA[Scrap gold]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61009.capital"><![CDATA[SCRAP GOLD]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.tooltip.61009"><![CDATA[Well-to-do Capitalists donate their scrap gold to the Antiquity Fair.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Carrots]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[CARROTS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Every stew needs plenty of carrots!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61014"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.goodname.61014.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8009000.goods.tooltip.61014"><![CDATA[Giant logs are used to stabilize the festival grounds.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Winterfest]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Deck the halls, bundle up, and let it snow! It's time for the Winter Festival!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Whoa! Look at all that snow! I can hardly believe that you made it to the event plaza, Mayor {PLAYERNAME}! Can you help us prepare for the Winter Festival?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[The beams and stable logs from your lumber yard are just the materials we need to build up our stands. Go out and get some so that we can start the construction!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Excellent! The builders are making so much progress. Keep it up!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[It's still snowing! Hm, we're going to need more wood so that the weight of the snow doesn't collapse the stands. Rev up your saws again! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Wow, it's definitely going to hold now! The stands look so festive covered in snow.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[I've got a great idea! Let's decorate the event plaza in the style of a wintery forrest! Plant some fir trees and mistletoe on your farm. We'll take care of the rest!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Fantastic! The Winter Festival looks like a snowy village in the Alps. How cozy!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Mmm, what's that delicious smell? The residents in your city have been baking cookies. When you go to collect their rent, they're sure to donate a fresh batch!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[So many cookies! Your residents have really outdone themselves this time. Great job!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Your residents love to bake and it's  the time of year where gingerbread men are on the menu. See if they'll donate a few when you pass by to collect rent!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Well done! Happy faces all around. What a wonderful festival!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Have you heard? Your residents want to play a round of Secret Santa! Collect their presents and you can hand them out later. This is going to be fun!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Way to go! Everyone is sure to get a treat with this mountain of gifts!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[Brrr, it's freezing out here! How about a nice, hot spiced punch for the Winter Festival? That'll warm everyone up. Plant grapes and raspberries on your farm!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[Yum! The punch is delicious. Such a lovely way to warm up!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[Did you remember the gifts? It looks like most of the residents aren't too thrilled with what they received. Typical! Come on, let's go gather them up and re-distribute them!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[The Winter Festival was a complete success! Everything went according to plan. We'll have to do this again next year!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[Could you do us one more favor? There are so many old, dried out fir trees lying around the city. Help us clean up the city by collecting them!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[Awesome! Dried out trees can be a real fire hazard. Thanks for cleaning them up so quickly!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Fir tree]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[FIR TREE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[Big, beautiful, and lush! Get your ornaments ready!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61002"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61002.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61002"><![CDATA[Use to build stands or support beams, stable logs will always do the trick!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Grapes]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[GRAPES]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[The best fruits make the best winter punch!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Cookie]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[COOKIE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Need more homemade cookies? Here you go!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61005"><![CDATA[Gingerbread man]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61005.capital"><![CDATA[GINGERBREAD MAN]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61005"><![CDATA[Kids and adults both love to snack on freshly baked gingerbread men!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61006"><![CDATA[Gift]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61006.capital"><![CDATA[GIFT]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61006"><![CDATA[Everyone get's a gift at the Winter Festival. I wonder what's inside?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Old fir tree]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[OLD FIR TREE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[So many old fir trees - time to get rid of them!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61011"><![CDATA[Mistletoe]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61011.capital"><![CDATA[MISTLETOE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61011"><![CDATA[A smooch 'neath the mistletoe? How romantic! The perfect winter decoration!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61012"><![CDATA[Unwrapped gift]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61012.capital"><![CDATA[UNWRAPPED GIFT]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61012"><![CDATA[It's time to exchange gifts in Rising Cities. Re-distribute the gifts to make everyone happy!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61022"><![CDATA[Gingerbread man]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.goodname.61022.capital"><![CDATA[GINGERBREAD MAN]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.goods.tooltip.61022"><![CDATA[Kids and adults both love to snack on freshly baked gingerbread men!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Old fir tree]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8010000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[So many old fir trees. Time to throw them out!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Flea Market]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[The charity flea market is swinging through town for donations. How many can you collect?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Good news, Mayor! A charity flea market is coming to our city. Helping out would be great publicity!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[First, we need to prepare the city square for the event. Let’s gather some resources from the lumber mill.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Looking good! These resources will be essential to building the flea market.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Volunteers are now hard at work building the flea market. Let’s get them some fresh snacks from the farm!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[The flea market is finished! It seems like the snacks gave the volunteers the extra boost they needed.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Any good flea market needs a lot of fun items to sell. Let’s ask the citizens for donations when we collect rent.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[These donations are a great starting point. We still need more to fill out the flea market, though.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[We still need some more items to sell. Try asking the capitalists for an extra donation when you collect rent.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[This looks great! These donations will definitely sell!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[We’re just about done, and we almost sold out of everything! The press is looking for pictures of the mayor doing ordinary work. Why don’t you help clean up the streets?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[The flea market was a huge success! And look what I found between some old books... a permit for a beautiful Tenement!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61002"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61002.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.tooltip.61002"><![CDATA[Strengthen your Event Plaza for the flea market with these stable logs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Carrots]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[CARROTS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Crunchy carrots are a perfect and healthy snack!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Trash]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[TRASH]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[You collected this trash from the streets after the flea market.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61008"><![CDATA[Teddy]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61008.capital"><![CDATA[TEDDY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.tooltip.61008"><![CDATA[Donated teddy bears from the homes of workers.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61009"><![CDATA[Jewelry]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61009.capital"><![CDATA[JEWELRY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.tooltip.61009"><![CDATA[Capitalists donated gold trinkets to sell at the flea market.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61013"><![CDATA[Vases]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.goodname.61013.capital"><![CDATA[VASES]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.goods.tooltip.61013"><![CDATA[Decorative vases from capitalist households.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[TRASH]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8011000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Trash that visitors to the flea market threw away.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Valentine's Day]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[TODO: Newsscreeen]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[It's almost Valentine's Day, but love is definitely not in the air. You'll need to act fast to get your unromantic citizens in the mood for love!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Why not throw a Valentine's Dance on the event plaza? The workers will need ebony to transform the plaza into the perfect romantic setting.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Way to go! You're off to a great start. There are still a few bare spots that could use a little improvement!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Collect more materials so that the Valentine's Dance can go off without a hitch!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Looking good! The dance floor looks great! You've really outdone yourself. Now we just need to invite the guests.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Grow red roses on your farm to give to each guest. That should work like a charm!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Fantastic! We're sure to have a lot more guests now!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[What about a small buffet for the dance? Strawberries are considered to be quite the seductive fruit. Grow a few bushels on your farm and see if it's true!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Great job. Strawberries certainly live up to their reputation! However, we'll need an alternative for the guests with allergies.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Sweet, red cherries are the perfect choice to romantic food and drink. Grow enough cherries on your farm, so that we'll have enough for everyone!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Perfect! Now everyone can enjoy some sweet fruit!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Here's an idea: Collect phone numbers from citizens the next time you go to collect their rent. Then you can mix up the numbers and each resident can choose one. Blind dates for everyone!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Impressive! Look how many people have participated! Now we just need to mix up the numbers and...NO! A gust of wind!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[The wind blew the phone numbers all over the city. You'll need to collect them all so the citizens can go on their blind dates!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[You're the world's best mayor! Let the raffle begin!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[The couples have found each other, but blind dates can be a bit awkward. Bake a few cupcakes to lighten the mood!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[Sweets for the sweethearts!  Look at everyone getting along!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[The Valentine's Dance was a huge success! The city is now full of lovebirds exchanging love letters and diamond rings. Collect the presents and make sure they get to the intended recipients!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[How wonderful! Your city can now claim the title "City of Love"! What do you think of that? Congratulations!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Cherry]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[CHERRY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[Red, round, and sweet. If you're not into strawberries, there are always cherries!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61014"><![CDATA[Ebony]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61014.capital"><![CDATA[EBONY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61014"><![CDATA[The dark ebony wood will compliment the red Valentine's decorations in the Event Plaza.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61011"><![CDATA[Red rose]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61011.capital"><![CDATA[RED ROSE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61011"><![CDATA[A bouquet of red roses is the perfect way to declare your love!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Strawberry]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[STRAWBERRY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Strawberries are a must-have for any romantic meal!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Phone number]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[PHONE NUMBER]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Need a few more digits to set up blind dates? Here you go!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Scattered phone number]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[SCATTERED PHONE NUMBER]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[Collecting phone numbers is hard work, looks like these were blown away!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61005"><![CDATA[Cupcake]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61005.capital"><![CDATA[CUPCAKE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61005"><![CDATA[Yummy! A cherry-strawberry muffin! Sweets for your sweety!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61008"><![CDATA[Love letter]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61008.capital"><![CDATA[LOVE LETTER]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61008"><![CDATA[Your workers love to write letters to their sweethearts. How romantic!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61009"><![CDATA[Diamond ring]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.goodname.61009.capital"><![CDATA[DIAMOND RING]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.goods.tooltip.61009"><![CDATA[Sparing no expense, your capitalists give their sweeties sparkling ring bling!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[PHONE NUMBER LIST]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8012000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Collect these lists to re-gain phone numbers blown away by the wind!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Easter]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[It's Easter and there's lots to get done before the celebration. Hop to it!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Spring has sprung! Aspiring Easter bunnies are ready to dye and hide lots of eggs. Time to get started with the prep work, Mayor. Hop to it!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Look out! After a long, dreary winter, the Event Plaza looks a little swampy. You'll need to reinforce the ground with wood from your lumber mill!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Looks good and stable! The wood reinforcements should hold up. Great job!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Chop-chop, Mayor! No sleeping on the job. Whip this place into shape with some decorations. Daffodils from the farm and solid ebony should do nicely!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Beautiful! Atchoo...oops, sorry! It certainly smells like Spring in here. A bit of hay fever just gives it an extra authentic touch!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[You can't have Easter without the dyed eggs. Crank out some organic eggs from your farm and collect egg dye from your residents the next time you collect rent!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Well, color me surprised! You finished that in a flash. The eggs are dyed and hidden. Let's do this!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Wow! Your residents are so generous! They've decided to donate choco-bunnies to all of the kiddies at the Easter celebration. Go door-to-door to collect the chocolate and to say thanks!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[*Omnomnom* These choco-bunnies are delish! But there's no time for snacking right now. You've still got work to do!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Uh oh! Your "Easter bunny" helpers got carried away with hiding the eggs. They've hidden them all over the city, instead of the Event Plaza. Help them search for the eggs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[If you weren't already mayor, you could have been a professional egg hunter. Well, if such a thing even existed. Congrats! You found them all!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Um, Mayor? We've got another problem. The Easter eggs...they're...hatching?! Looks like some of them weren't hard-boiled and now there are fluffy little chicks running around the city! We're going to need wood to build them some chicken coops!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Wow! Talk about a strange day! All the chicks have been found and moved to a farm where they'll have plenty of space.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[We're running short on time. The baby chick fiasco put us off schedule. There's still an Easter bonfire to organize. Quick! There's brushwood at the lumber mill and perhaps your residents still have old fir trees from the holidays!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[Not bad, Mayor! That's an impressive mountain of  dried wood. The bonfire will be blazing in no time!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[Don't forget. Your guests will need some refreshments while  sitting around the bonfire. How about a traditional Easter snack? The bakery can whip up some loaves of Easter bread!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[Between the choco-bunnies and Easter bread, I'm stuffed! Ok, maybe I'll just have one more slice...]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[Almost time to light the bonfire! But first, let's make a toast. Make sure everyone has something to drink. Beer for the workers and champagne for the capitalists!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[Well done! The Easter bonfire is perfect: big, warm, and bright! The guests are gobbling up the Easter bread and clinking glasses! This celebration is your biggest hit yet!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61002"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61002.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61002"><![CDATA[Perfect for reinforcing your Event Plaza!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Organic eggs]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[ORGANIC EGGS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Happy chickens make happy eggs! Ready to paint!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Egg dye]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[EGG DYE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Dye your organic eggs with a rainbow of colors!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61005"><![CDATA[Easter bread]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61005.capital"><![CDATA[EASTER BREAD]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61005"><![CDATA[Fresh Easter bread - a delightful treat for your hungry guests!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61006"><![CDATA[Choco-bunny]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61006.capital"><![CDATA[CHOCO-BUNNY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61006"><![CDATA[Are your residents short on choco-bunnies? Get more here!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Easter eggs]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[EASTER EGGS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[Colorful Easter eggs are a must-have!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61009"><![CDATA[Champagne]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61009.capital"><![CDATA[CHAMPAGNE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61009"><![CDATA[A bit of bubbly for the capitalists. Raise your glasses!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61011"><![CDATA[Daffodil]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61011.capital"><![CDATA[DAFFODIL]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61011"><![CDATA[Arrange a lovely bouquet or plant a few in your garden. Daffodils are the essence of springtime! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61012"><![CDATA[Old fir tree]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61012.capital"><![CDATA[OLD FIR TREE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61012"><![CDATA[The old, dried up remains of the holiday season. Perfect bonfire material!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61014"><![CDATA[Ebony]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61014.capital"><![CDATA[EBONY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61014"><![CDATA[Decorative ebony for a real touch of class!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61015"><![CDATA[Brushwood]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61015.capital"><![CDATA[BRUSHWOOD]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61015"><![CDATA[Bits of brushwood to spark your Easter bonfire!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61016"><![CDATA[Chick]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61016.capital"><![CDATA[CHICK]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61016"><![CDATA[Cute little baby chicks are always a big Easter hit!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61017"><![CDATA[Beer]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.goodname.61017.capital"><![CDATA[BEER]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.goods.tooltip.61017"><![CDATA[Students and workers love to toss back a few cold ones!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Easter nest]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Easter nests are the perfect hiding place for Easter eggs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.boulder.bouldername.43002"><![CDATA[Nest]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8013000.boulder.boulderflavour.43002"><![CDATA[Find the baby chicks hiding in these nests!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Biker Rally]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Look at all these motorcycles! Bikers are streaming into town for the rally. Vroooom!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Mayor, this spring time weather makes me want to jump on my motorcycle and take a road trip. I know we're so busy here in town, but maybe instead, we could host a biker rally right here!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[We can? Really?! Awesome! Let's start the prep work. Of course, we need to reinforce the Event Plaza so it can hold those heavy bikes.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[The Event Plaza could probably hold up a tank or two. Nice job!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Bikers do love to eat. We'll need plenty of fries and beer. Grow enough potatoes on the farm and place an order at the micro-brewery for beer!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Just in time! The first bikers are starting to roll into town!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Uh oh, Mayor! We've got a problem! Some of the residents have been complaining about the motorcycle noise. They've written complaint letters and you need to collect them the next time rent is due!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Picking up the complain letters personally was a genius move, Mayor! Well done!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Beer and hot dogs for everyone! We're almost out of brown ale and our meat situation doesn't look so hot. I've got it! We just need to grow some soybeans on the farm and then the bakery can make tofu dogs! No one will even know the difference!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[See? I told you! The bikers can't tell the difference between the tofu dogs and the real thing!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Hooray! It's time for the motorcycle parade! Some of the bikers aren't wearing helmets. That's not safe at all. And Chief Slowgo definitely doesn't look pleased! Let's borrow some helmets from the residents.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[What a thrill! The parade was a big hit! Keep it up and we'll start getting international recognition for our celebrations!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61014"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61014.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.tooltip.61014"><![CDATA[Reinforce the Event Plaza for the Biker Rally with some reliable logs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61018"><![CDATA[Brown ale keg]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61018.capital"><![CDATA[BROWN ALE KEG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.tooltip.61018"><![CDATA[Bikers are a thirsty bunch, you'll definitely need a few kegs of brown ale!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Complaint letter]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[COMPLAINT LETTER]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Collecting complaint letters can be difficult - get them here instead!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Soybeans]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[SOYBEANS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[The main ingredient in tofu dogs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61005"><![CDATA[Tofu dogs]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61005.capital"><![CDATA[TOFU DOGS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.tooltip.61005"><![CDATA[Tofu dogs taste (almost) just like real hot dogs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61011"><![CDATA[Helmet]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61011.capital"><![CDATA[HELMET]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.tooltip.61011"><![CDATA[Safety first! Every biker needs a helmet!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61020"><![CDATA[Tofu sausage]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61020.capital"><![CDATA[TOFU SAUSAGE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.tooltip.61020"><![CDATA[Tofu dogs taste (almost) just like real hot dogs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61006"><![CDATA[Helmet]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.goodname.61006.capital"><![CDATA[HELMET]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8014000.goods.tooltip.61006"><![CDATA[Safety first! Every biker needs a helmet!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Children's Festival]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Think of the children! It's time to do  something just for them. What about a Children's Festival? ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Oh man, I'm really beat! My niece is in town. I've taken her everywhere, but she still says the city is too boring for kids. She's a smart alec, for sure, but maybe a Children's Festival will change her mind!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[This will be a big challenge, Mayor. Especially since we have to keep safety a priority. Lots of hay should do the trick!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Great! Soft hay and rounded edges will really prevent some nasty accidents!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Let's try to set a good example and avoid pumping the kids full of candy. How about organic apples? We can grow them right on the farm!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Yum, crunchy apples and...tomatoes? Ah, good thinking! The people in this town are crazy about tomatoes!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[A Children's Festival is the perfect opportunity for a toy swap. Collect old toys when you go to pick up the next rent and the kids can choose a toy at the festival.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Look at all the smiling faces! Let's go play a game with the kids!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Whoa! That escalated quickly! You were supposed to keep things under control, Mayor. Now there are balloons and soccer balls all over the city. Could you at least help me collect them?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Whew! Did we get them all? Looks like it. Fantastic! Thanks for your help!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Well, whaddya know, Mayor? Looks like this city isn't so boring after all. The kids had a great time and made some finger paintings to say thanks. You can collect them the next time rent is due!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[What a great day! The Children's Festival was a success and my niece is definitely singing a new tune!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61011"><![CDATA[Hay]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61011.capital"><![CDATA[HAY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.tooltip.61011"><![CDATA[Soft hay for the Children's Festival, safe and fun!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Organic apple]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[ORGANIC APPLE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Sweet organic apples are a healthy treat for growing kids!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Old toys]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[OLD TOYS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[You'd rather play with the kids, instead of collecting old toys? You can pick them up here!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Balloons]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[BALLOONS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[Don't feel like chasing balloons all over the city? Then take these!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61016"><![CDATA[Soccer ball]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61016.capital"><![CDATA[SOCCER BALL]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.tooltip.61016"><![CDATA[Don't feel like chasing soccer balls down the road? Here are a few you can use!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61006"><![CDATA[Finger painting]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.goodname.61006.capital"><![CDATA[FINGER PAINTING]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.goods.tooltip.61006"><![CDATA[Aww! Cute finger paintings to hang up on the fridge or in your office!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Balloons]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Collect the balloons quickly before they cause an accident!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.boulder.bouldername.43002"><![CDATA[Soccer ball]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8015000.boulder.boulderflavour.43002"><![CDATA[Collect the soccer balls before someone gets hurt!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Classic Car Show]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Rev your engine and show off your hot rod at the Classic Car Show. You might go home with 1st place!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Mayor Tenenbaum, from our sister city Newfield, is looking for a location to hold a Classic Car Show. We could host that, right?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[After the race, the cars will be on display for the visitors. We're a little short on parking spaces, so we'll need to expand. Some soft hay will also protect the cars from getting scratched up!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Wow, that was quick! Thank goodness, too! The race has already started and the cars are on their way here!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[The classic cars are still a long way off. The drivers are sure to be hungry when they arrive. Plant some potatoes and carrots on your farm. You can feed them french fries and salad!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Great! Everything looks ready! We just have to wait for the cars to cross the finish line!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[What a rush! The first classic cars are crossing the finish line! But what's that over there? A few of the cars have lost parts along the way. Those could turn into real road hazards. Hurry and clean them up!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Whew! The streets are clear, but the cars look worse for wear.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Those beautiful cars! It's tough to see them in this condition. Why not ask your residents for tools the next time you collect rent!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[I knew we could count on your residents. The classic cars look good as new! Time for the awards ceremony!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Mayor, we've got a problem! The prizes have disappeared! Quick! The brickyard can produce some clay figurines for the participants and we can crown the winner with laurels from your farm. ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Hooray! The race and award ceremony were a big hit! Time to go look at the classic cars.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.layer.success.flavour.upselling"><![CDATA[You successfully purchased the top prize!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61011"><![CDATA[Hay]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61011.capital"><![CDATA[HAY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.tooltip.61011"><![CDATA[Soft hay protects valuable classic cars from scratches.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Carrots]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[CARROTS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Crunchy veggies for healthy Classic Car Show snacks.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Laurel]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[LAUREL]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[Even the Ancient Greeks used laurels to crown their victors.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Car parts]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[CAR PARTS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[Haven't found all of the car parts? Get more here.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61019"><![CDATA[Figurine]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61019.capital"><![CDATA[FIGURINE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.tooltip.61019"><![CDATA[A little souvenir for all Classic Car Show participants.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Toolbox]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[TOOLBOX]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Contains any tool that you might need for repairing classic cars.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Lost car parts]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8016000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Collect discarded car parts to repair classic cars later!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Art Expo]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Dust off your paints and paintbrushes, it's time for the Art Expo! Win cool prizes while the whole city takes part!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[It's time to bring a bit of culture to the city, Mayor! Let's organize an interactive Art Expo. The residents can take part in workshops, learn about various crafts and take home their works of art!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Before the art expo workshops can begin, the multi-functional gallery needs to be built! You'll need space and materials for painting, sculpting...the works! Produce enough wood to make your artistic vision a reality!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Looks great, Mayor! Now we'll just have to see what kind of masterpieces your residents create!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[For the pottery class, we'll need lots of clay. And tomatoes. Before you ask, I've got no idea why we need tomatoes either, Mayor. Never question an artist's integrity!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Those bowls look amazing! Hard to believe what you can make out of clay and a few tomatoes. Looks like you made something too, Mayor. What exactly is it supposed to be?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[A woodworking woodshop! How wonderful! We just have to wrangle up some spare roof beams and paint for decorating. The workers are sure to have a few old paint cans lying around!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Wow! Take a look at these creations. They look so professional! I'd hang a few pictures in these stylish wooden frames, for sure!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[There's even a workshop for the kids! The Crafts for Kids area needs costume jewelry and friendship bracelets. Those sound like just the things for the capitalists and students to donate!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Great job! This just goes to show that you're never too old or young for art!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Uh oh! Where there's art, there's Pranksy the notorious street artist. He's been displaying odd little statues all around the city. Maybe it's an artistic statement, but also a traffic hazard, thanks to all of the rubbernecking drivers.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Whew! That was close! The statues have been cleaned up and the workshops have been a huge hit. Give yourself a pat on the back!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.layer.success.flavour.upselling"><![CDATA[Way to go! You purchased the top prize!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61014"><![CDATA[Log]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61014.capital"><![CDATA[LOG]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.tooltip.61014"><![CDATA[Stable logs turn the Event Plaza into a multi-functional art gallery!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61019"><![CDATA[Clay]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61019.capital"><![CDATA[CLAY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.tooltip.61019"><![CDATA[Sculptors-in-training need plenty of clay from the brickyard!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61008"><![CDATA[Paint Can]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61008.capital"><![CDATA[PAINT CAN]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.tooltip.61008"><![CDATA[Collect cans of paint from workers and spread the colors on the canvasses!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61009"><![CDATA[Costume jewelry]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61009.capital"><![CDATA[COSTUME JEWELRY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.tooltip.61009"><![CDATA[Combine pieces of old costume jewelry from wealthy residents to craft into trendy, new accessories!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Friendship bracelets]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[FRIENDSHIP BRACELETS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Colorful friendship bracelets woven by arts-n-crafty students!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Mini-he statue]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[MINI-HE STATUE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[Find the mini-he statues hidden all over town by notorious street artist, Pranksy.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61016"><![CDATA[Mini-she statue]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.goodname.61016.capital"><![CDATA[MINI-SHE STATUE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.goods.tooltip.61016"><![CDATA[Find the mini-she statues hidden all over town by notorious street artist, Pranksy.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Street art]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Pranksy the street artist makes his artistic statement by hiding odd little statues all over the city.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.boulder.bouldername.43002"><![CDATA[Street art]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8017000.boulder.boulderflavour.43002"><![CDATA[Pranksy the street artist makes his artistic statement by hiding odd little statues all over the city.]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Rising Cities is turning one year old! Time to take a look back at what you accomplished this year. Join in the fun!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Look at how the time flies, Mayor! Let's celebrate our city's birthday by re-creating some of the best events from the past year. It's party time!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Valentine's Day sure made lots of residents swoooon! Crank up the romance again with rose bouquets and love letters!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[I'm blushing! Is it warm in here or just me? Not all residents are into that mushy stuff, though. Here's a letter from a fan of our cool Winter Festival!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[The snow! The presents! The Winter Festival was positively magical, Mayor. With mistletoe and gingerbread men, we can re-live all of the memories!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Yummy gingerbread! I'm stuffed. A mini Winter Festival in the summer is nice, but can you guess which event the residents asked for next?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Our springtime Easter event was a real hit! Everyone in town had fun dyeing eggs, hunting for eggs, catching baby chicks. We can re-create it all! Just don't forget the chocolate bunnies!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[What a treat! The kids in this town really love Easter. We ought to make a note of that. Plenty of candy is right up their alley! So, what's up next?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Spooky, scary Halloween! Trick-or-treating is always a fun time. The residents love collecting candy and carving jack-o-lanterns from pumpkins!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[No ghouls here! Just lots of fun! The compliments are pouring in...]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[You've gotten quite popular, Mayor. Congratulations on the successful year! We need to throw a party to mark the occasion. Help me get some cake and collect the party hats strewn about the town!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Oh, my hero! Once again, thanks to you, the event was a smashing success! Three cheers for our wonderful mayor and happy birthday, Rising Cities!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.layer.success.flavour.upselling"><![CDATA[Way to go! You purchased the top prize!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61003"><![CDATA[Rose Bouquet]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61003.capital"><![CDATA[ROSE BOUQUET]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61003"><![CDATA[Nothing says romance like a bouquet of bright red roses!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Love letter]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[LOVE LETTER]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Love is in the air, again! Collect love letters from your residents.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Pumpkin]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[PUMPKIN]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[Produce spooktacular jack-o-lantern pumpkins on your farm!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Easter Eggs]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[EASTER EGGS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[Re-live memories of Easter with these colorful eggs!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61021"><![CDATA[Gingerbread Man]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61021.capital"><![CDATA[GINGERBREAD MAN]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61021"><![CDATA[Yummy gingerbread men are a delicious treat year-round.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61006"><![CDATA[Chocolate Bunny]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61006.capital"><![CDATA[CHOCOLATE BUNNY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61006"><![CDATA[Hippity hop! Chocolate bunnies from your residents let you savor sweet Easter memories!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61011"><![CDATA[Mistletoe]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61011.capital"><![CDATA[MISTLETOE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61011"><![CDATA[Grow mistletoe on your farm and your residents can smooch all year long!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61012"><![CDATA[Candy]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61012.capital"><![CDATA[CANDY]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61012"><![CDATA[Mmm, sweets, lollipops, and chocolate! What would Halloween be without candy?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61005"><![CDATA[Birthday Cake]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61005.capital"><![CDATA[BIRTHDAY CAKE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61005"><![CDATA[Bake the best birthday cake for the best city - yours!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61016"><![CDATA[Party hat]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.goodname.61016.capital"><![CDATA[PARTY HATS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.goods.tooltip.61016"><![CDATA[Put on your hats and get ready to party!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Hidden Eggs]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Find the colorful Easter eggs hidden around the city!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.boulder.bouldername.43002"><![CDATA[Lost Hats]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8018000.boulder.boulderflavour.43002"><![CDATA[A gust of wind blew the party hats away! Go find them!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Winter Games]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Bundle up! The Winter Games have arrived! Get ready for athleticism, sportsmanship, and awesome prizes!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Don't you just love winter, Mayor? The weather's perfect for all sorts of winter sports. We should host a Winter Games event, so fans and athletes from all over can get in on the fun!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Time to get to it, Mayor! If we're going to pull this off, we'll need lots of flagpoles so the visiting fans and athletes can show their hometown pride!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[We're off to a great start! I've got a feeling that the Winter Games are going to be a big hit!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[The spectators are going to need something to munch. With so many competitors, the games will take awhile. Chips and peanuts are always a big hit!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Delish! No rumbling stomachs in these crowds. All eyes will be on the ice!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[How could we have forgotten the flags? Empty flagpoles look a bit silly. Our residents can help pitch in with sewing them and you just have to pick them up with the rent!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Wonderful craftsmanship, wouldn't you say? I knew we could rely on our residents!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Everyone's gone above and beyond for the Winter Games. We've got so many flags, that they outnumber the poles. We'll need to produce more flagpoles, if we want our games to be the best!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[You're really on top of everything, Mayor! The flags are waving high above the city in a sea of color!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Fans and flags everywhere! The crowd is even larger than we expected, however. We're definitely going to need more snacks!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Fantastic! Now we've got enough food for everyone!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Mayor! Several bus-loads of new competitors just arrived in town! It's a pleasant surprise, but a surprise nonetheless! We'll need more flags to help cheer them on during the games!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Stunning! With this many flags, the city's covered in color!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[What if we built statues commemorating various winter sports? I think that's a task for the brickyard; they're raring to go. They just need the materials!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[Top notch! The statues look amazing, like something right out of ancient times!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[We'll need to re-stock the snacks, Mayor. People are starting to ask for seconds...and thirds. Don't make them wait! See if the farmers can help us out!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[That was a close call, but you did it! Bright eyes and full bellies all around!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[The spectators need something to wash down all those salty snacks. I think the brewery can whip up some sports drinks. That'll put some pep in their steps!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[So refreshing! These sports drinks have plenty of electrolytes to keep the crowd energized!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.10"><![CDATA[A few more winter sports have been added to the program. You'll need to go back to the brickyard to pick up more statues. They've already got their hammers ready!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.10"><![CDATA[Well done! Now we have a statue depicting every winter sport under the sun!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.11"><![CDATA[The games have started and it's nearly time to declare all of the winners. Each victor will be rewarded with a flag. Collect more from your residents!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.11"><![CDATA[Wonderful! The first winners are already on the podiums. Look at their flags wave in the breeze!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.12"><![CDATA[What a day! Food, fun, and sportsmanship! The athletes are exhausted from the competition. Let's surprise them with some refreshing sports drinks!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.12"><![CDATA[Now that's what I call refreshment! Another successful event all thanks to you, Mayor!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61023"><![CDATA[Flagpole]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61023.capital"><![CDATA[FLAGPOLE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.tooltip.61023"><![CDATA[Fans from around the world need flagpoles to hoist their colors!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61024"><![CDATA[Snacks]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61024.capital"><![CDATA[SNACKS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.tooltip.61024"><![CDATA[Watching winter sports and eating yummy snacks is an unbeatable combo!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61025"><![CDATA[Sports Drink]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61025.capital"><![CDATA[SPORTS DRINK]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.tooltip.61025"><![CDATA[Make sure the visiting athletes get plenty of electrolytes with sports drinks!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61026"><![CDATA[Statues]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61026.capital"><![CDATA[STATUES]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.tooltip.61026"><![CDATA[Statues are a great way to remind everyone of the sportsmanship of the Winter Games!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Flags]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[FLAGS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8019000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Hoist a flag atop a flagpole and show pride for your local athletes!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Rock Fest]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.newsscreen.flavour"><![CDATA[Ready to rock? The city's buzzing about the big Rock Fest coming to town. There's plenty of work to do, so jump right in! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Remember the Biker Rally, Mayor? The bikers had such a great time that they'd like to come back to our fair city for a Rock Fest. Let's go!  ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[First things first, we'll need a sturdy stage that can withstand anything these rockers can throw at it! Quality plywood from the lumber mill ought to do the trick.  ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Now that's what I call a main stage! Stable and ready for action. Would you like to try a stage dive, Mayor?  ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Headbanging can be pretty exhausting, so we also need to make sure that out visitors have plenty to eat and drink. I know! Let's serve pretzels and beer!  ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Yum! I love the smell of fresh pretzels! And I just know the concert goers will love this freshly brewed beer! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[The residents are so excited about the Rock Fest that they even bought extra tickets so that anyone who wants to can attend the festival! Pick up the tickets from them and some extra mulch, while you're at it!  ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Rockin'! Isn't it great how we can always rely on the generosity of our residents? ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Mayor, quick! The crowds are getting restless and fighting over concert merchandise lying in the street! Help the fans calm down and clean up the streets so everyone stays safe! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Whew! That was close, but you handled it like a pro. Thanks, Mayor! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[It's showtime! The bands have arrived and are ready to rock our socks off! Let's show them our appreciation by passing out lighters for everyone to hold up during the songs. It'll be unforgettable! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Awesome! I haven't been to a show like that in years. The bands were amazing and the visitors loved it. Another successful event, boss! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.layer.success.flavour.upselling"><![CDATA[Way to go! You purchased the top prize!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61014"><![CDATA[Plywood]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61014.capital"><![CDATA[PLYWOOD]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.tooltip.61014"><![CDATA[Produce sturdy plywood in the lumber mill!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61021"><![CDATA[Pretzel]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61021.capital"><![CDATA[PRETZEL]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.tooltip.61021"><![CDATA[Bake delicious pretzels in the bakery to feed the hungry crowd!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Concert Tickets]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[CONCERT TICKET]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Collect donated concert tickets from your residents to help promote the Rock Fest!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61015"><![CDATA[Mulch]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61015.capital"><![CDATA[MULCH]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.tooltip.61015"><![CDATA[Produce mulch in the mill and you'll have less of a muddy mess to clean up later!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61007"><![CDATA[Calm Fans]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61007.capital"><![CDATA[CALM FANS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.tooltip.61007"><![CDATA[Calm fans are the key to throwing a fun festival that's also safe!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61016"><![CDATA[Concert Merchandise]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61016.capital"><![CDATA[CONCERT MERCHANDISE]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.tooltip.61016"><![CDATA[Concert merchandise is the perfect Rock Fest souvenir!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61008"><![CDATA[Lighter]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61008.capital"><![CDATA[LIGHTER]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.tooltip.61008"><![CDATA[Set the mood by waving a few lighters in the air! Ask your workers to donate a few.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61027"><![CDATA[Teddy bear]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.goodname.61027.capital"><![CDATA[TEDDY BEAR]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.goods.tooltip.61027"><![CDATA[Teddy bears from your students are great keepsakes to help the bands remember this rockin' festival!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Rioting Fans]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Prevent hyped up fans from blocking the streets and causing a ruckus!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.boulder.bouldername.43002"><![CDATA[Abandoned Merchandise]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8020000.boulder.boulderflavour.43002"><![CDATA[Looks like someone forgot to pick up this merchandise!]]></item>
 </category>
 <category name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000">
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.name"><![CDATA[Soccer Party]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.preview.flavour"><![CDATA[Hey, Mayor! You'll get a real kick out of this exciting soccer-themed adventure!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Yo, boss! Whaddya say we roll out the green carpet for the athletes attending our big soccer party? Rustle up some grass from the boys on the farm, would ya?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.1"><![CDATA[Way to go, chief! That's one mean and lean soccer field. Our work's not done yet. Let's go.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Ok, time for the warm-up match. There's the whistle... and... Why are the players twiddling their thumbs? Where's the... oh. Oops. Forgot the ball.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.2"><![CDATA[Niiiice! Can't have a kickoff without something to kick, am I right? I think I'm coming down with a case of soccer fever. ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Hole-y moly! Look at the bleachers; they're full of termites. They need to be replaced before the competition begins or we'll be in a whole lot of trouble!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.3"><![CDATA[Perfect! The fans will be safe and sound in these bleachers. Wanna test them out and start a wave?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Aw crud! The players are wandering around the field like hypnotized chickens. Wait, I've got it! Some chalk lines on the field should help.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.4"><![CDATA[Top notch work, Mayor! Outlining the field in chalk puts us right up there with the big leagues.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Now the ball's rolling! But... the spectators still look a bit bored. Maybe these custom fan scarves will get them pumped!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.5"><![CDATA[Fan-tastic! Get it? The fans can show their team spirit and I gotta say that these scarves are quite the fashion statement, as well!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[It's all fun and games until the stomach rumbles are louder than the action on the field. Better break out the snacks before we have a riot on our hands!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.6"><![CDATA[Now that's what I call fast food! You've got the public eating right out of your hand.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[I didn't mean for you to put everyone in a food coma. Perhaps a cold brewski or two will shake things up a bit! What's soccer without beer?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.7"><![CDATA[OLÈ, OLÈ, OLÈ! GREAT JOB! *HIC*... WHAT? WHADDISAY?]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[It's go time! Hold up! Where'd the balls go? Have the refs been drinking or something?<br><br>Oh, right.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.8"><![CDATA[You're on a roll! Keep this up and the fans might just name you MVP.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.running.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[Whew! Finally kickoff time! The fans might need a few more baked snacks. That'll keep their hands busy if the game doesn't go their way.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.challenge.9"><![CDATA[GOOOOAAAAAAL! And it's a tie! Everyone's going home happy. Gotta love a good soccer match!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.layer.success.flavour.upselling"><![CDATA[Way to go! You purchased the top prize!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61001"><![CDATA[Grass]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61001.capital"><![CDATA[GRASS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.tooltip.61001"><![CDATA[No synthetic turf here! Play a match or ten on 100% natural green grass.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61004"><![CDATA[Soccer Balls]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61004.capital"><![CDATA[SOCCER BALLS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.tooltip.61004"><![CDATA[Dribble these balls down the field like a pro. Don’t forget: no hands allowed!]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61014"><![CDATA[Plywood]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61014.capital"><![CDATA[PLYWOOD]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.tooltip.61014"><![CDATA[Turn every seat into the best seat in the house with bleachers made of homegrown plywood.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61026"><![CDATA[Chalk]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61026.capital"><![CDATA[CHALK]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.tooltip.61026"><![CDATA[Fine white chalk on the field keeps the fun safely inbounds.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61016"><![CDATA[Scarves]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61016.capital"><![CDATA[SCARVES]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.tooltip.61016"><![CDATA[Show your true colors with an official team scarf! ]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61018"><![CDATA[Beer]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61018.capital"><![CDATA[BEER]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.tooltip.61018"><![CDATA[Crack open a cold one, while you sit back and watch the match.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61024"><![CDATA[Snacks]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61024.capital"><![CDATA[SNACKS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.tooltip.61024"><![CDATA[Healthy snacks! Local and fresh from the farm.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61005"><![CDATA[Baked Snacks]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.goodname.61005.capital"><![CDATA[BAKED SNACKS]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.goods.tooltip.61005"><![CDATA[Sports events are the perfect excuse to sneak in a bit of carbo-loading.]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.boulder.bouldername.43001"><![CDATA[Fan Merch]]></item>
  <item name="rcl.citysquarequests.8021000.boulder.boulderflavour.43001"><![CDATA[Real fans don’t just go to the games; they dress the part to support their home team.]]></item>
 </category>
</language>
